<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Adi Sharma</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Adi Sharma</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Opinionated thoughts on trust</title><link>/posts/trust/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/trust/</guid><description>&lt;p>Recently the topic of trust has been on my mind. Trust seems to be the most basic/atomic construct of value at all levels of organization:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Trust within self&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Trust between people&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Trust in the government&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Trust in institutions&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Trust in the cosmic/spiritual&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>It seems to be the undercurrent that governs most of human collaboration. But what does it come down to? How do you build it? Maintain it?&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-core-of-trust">The Core of Trust&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A hot take is it realistically comes down to two things:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Win</title><link>/posts/win/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/win/</guid><description>&lt;p>How does one win at life?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Cheeky title. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit of a loaded question and one that changes over time. Currently, my answer to this is:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Work out every day&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Eat healthy&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Get good sleep&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Inculcate gratefulness&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Be disciplined about my work/craft of choice&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Be persistent and unrelenting in my pursuit of my goals&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Work hard and follow through (both equally important)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Take risks&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Surround myself with really really good people who care and be the best friend/coworker/partner I can be. Show up the best way I can in those relationships.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Be a force for good in the world.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Lead my life with integrity, purpose, resolve and passion.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol></description></item><item><title>quick ramblings on turning 26</title><link>/posts/26/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/26/</guid><description>&lt;p>wow. i can&amp;rsquo;t believe i am 26. so much has happened over the past year. here are some huge events happened since 25&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>went to india to celebrate diwali in india in &amp;lsquo;23 with family. this was my first time actually visiting in like 6 years as a full blown adult. i technically did go in 22 as well but only went for 5.5 days which was not nearly enough and it felt mostly like a blur. also the sole purpose of that trip was for performing last rites for my grandpa who passed so nothing felt real.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>first time going back for a festival since immigrating to canada. had so many feeling but overwhelming one was that of change. the india/delhi i knew is now merely a figment of imagination. every now and then, i would get pangs of nostalgia; an ode to simpler times. but the vast majority of experiences felt uniquely dissimilar to what i had propped india up to be in my head&lt;/li>
&lt;li>being with family for a festival was another first in a while and was really fun! enjoyed hanging out with everyone and really cherished their company&lt;/li>
&lt;li>growing up, any time we&amp;rsquo;d visit back to india, it felt like most of our time was spent doing chores/paperwork related to banks/govts/property and other random stuff. this time was no different. however, having tasted american and canadian systems, india was a whole different level. the rules of the games are just quite simply different. bureaucratic red tape takes a whole new meaning there.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>my outsider/insider perspective was that just throwing money at the problem of for example opening a bank account was not sufficient. the only way to get things done fast there was knowing someone in the system who could expedite internal processes. idk the exact cause but likely downstream of being an insanely huge and relatively young country&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>hung out with frens @nyc after coming back. saw the squad. was really nice to see a lot of folks from college. it was very cool to see the life the people i knew incredibly well had built post uni. after uni, the suspace of life paths/action space truly proliferates in theory. however, entropy can take over and lead to these not being explore. so granted that, it was delightful to see that some friends were yet carving their own paths and truly leveraging the choose your own adventure phase of adulthood.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>went back to canada for holidays and had a good time with the fam. fam&amp;rsquo;s first holiday szn post move to calgary from grande prairie so it was cool to help them explore the city together. it was very heartening to hear that both ma and pa enjoyed calgary as a city a lot more than gp.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>quick context: earlier in 2023, through not small feat, i convinced and helped parents move from grande prairie to calgary in the hopes that they would be much happier than before.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>some memorable moments: mom being wiped out by a small kid on a bunny hill/ going to an outdoor pool in -20 celsius weather, going to sulfur mountains, going to normal mountains,&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>going to playspace (node of socratica in sf) for the first time. this was a meaningful moment for perhaps non obvious reasons. socratica was an org i started with aman while in uni in our final term. since then, ti&amp;rsquo;s grown massively (due to the fantastic ppl that are involved with the org now - truly a labor of love from the team/all invovled). however, living in sf, i&amp;rsquo;ve only been able to see the growth from afar. this was the first time i was able to feel and observe the impact with my own two eyes. that something i had worked on had grown so much and ppl were self-gathering/node-creating to spend time making things meaningful to them. &amp;lt;3. definitely a crazy moment&lt;/li>
&lt;li>running the golden gate half marathon. yet another pinch-me moment. had my eyes set on this for a while. my first (and longest) racing event since high school. prior to this, i&amp;rsquo;d ran x-country but longest distance was 10k. so this was a significant step up. to add on to this, i didn&amp;rsquo;t realize until a week before the race that what i thought to be a flat course actually had some 2500 ft of elevation! note to the reader: def carefully read through things before signing up for them. so that was something i hadn&amp;rsquo;t trained for. my goal went from trying to aim for sub 2 to just finishing the half. to add on that, sf had a crazy amount of rain and this was in marin county badlands by the golden gate bridge, making the entire course super muddy. happy to report i did finish! the race had turned from a normal half to a tough mudder lol. this was the first time in a while that i&amp;rsquo;d felt this proud of myself. meant a lot to me and i felt so good.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>housewarming party: hosted an intimate gathering with close friends for the new house that R and I moved into. albeit it was 8 months late, we got it done. had a great time! highlight was playing phone ping pong on the dining table 😀&lt;/li>
&lt;li>dad diagnosis: dad was diagnosed with a 80-90% blockage in his main coronary artery. this was crazy and changed everything. life felt like it flipped upside down in that moment. the next 3/4 months are hazy because so much stuff happened. to add on to woes, work started to go through the ringer. needless to say, this was one of those shrugging me back to reality moments and things changed. dad had to get a bypass.to make things more interesting, mom had a health scare during this as well. so much stuff ensued and i still feel myself getting emotional just thinking about this time again but safe to say this was the hardest 3 month period of my life so far. i could talk about this so much more but tldr was this made me deeply question everything i knew about life. coming upfront with the very concept of aliveness made me realize just how fickle existence is.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>quit my job: one of the realizations had from the last instance was that life is short and i should really do whatever the heck i want to do. while i did like my job, i so ended up putting in my notice in july for quitting my swe big tech job! had no immediate plans but knew i wanted to explore new things.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>solotravelled to cdmx/puertorico: felt like i needed this trip to give myself some breathing room after the big changes. this was so fun. i love travelling. it makes me feel come alive. i came back to sf refreshed and with more clarity. this was also momentous for so many reasons. the first time i took time off in the midst of so much uncertainty financially/emotionally/professionally/personally.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>building things: bufferring &amp;hellip;&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Socratica Commencement Manifesto</title><link>/posts/post-socratica-commencement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/post-socratica-commencement/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/adityas129/status/1495465853776769035">The tweet that started it all&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Below is the very first memo &lt;a href="https://amanmathur.com/home">Aman&lt;/a> and I sent out to the first set of attendees of the inaugural &lt;a href="https://x.com/socraticainfo">Socratica&lt;/a> session. For the uninitiated, Socratica is a community of builders, entrepreneurs, and creators that Aman and I started at the University of Waterloo. Since it&amp;rsquo;s inception, it&amp;rsquo;s really taken off and expanded to 28 official cities in six different countries (and many more unofficial offshoot ones). A longer blog post on all things Socratica from my POV has been in works for quite some time but I promise I&amp;rsquo;ll eventually finish it (and I&amp;rsquo;ll link it here when I do). In the meanwhile, here&amp;rsquo;s the memo - short, sweet but to the point:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Microthoughts</title><link>/posts/twitter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/twitter/</guid><description>&lt;p>Seldom, certain hard earned aphorisms that reveal how the world really works surface in my day to day life that I want to store for record-keeping purposes. The reason being; while these learnings are quite localized, they seem to offer a lens into our ever-so-complicated world. Yes, in another world, I would just use Twitter/X &amp;hellip; I have an intuitive resistance to use Twitter as such. Call it contrarian, subverting the status quo, a small show of resistance againstherd-seeking mentality or what have you. This may change - I have though learnt to listen to my gut more than I did before.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Thank you Teachers</title><link>/posts/tyty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/tyty/</guid><description>&lt;p>As I spend my time pent up at home during quarantine, I came to learn that one of my chemistry teachers back in high school moved down the street from our place! That was very cool and sent me down a memory lane and a flashback of high school. This teacher in particular was somebody that I always had a great time learning from. In addition to teaching Chemistry in an awesome way, she was always open to talk about life in general and as teenagers learning to take baby-steps into adulthood, these riffing sessions were so interesting. That lead me to think about the impact that teachers have had in my life. I think teachers are so underappreciated in our society. Throughout my education, so many teachers have helped shape me and lead me to become the person I am today. To them I say, thank you. Thank you for believing in me when I sometimes didn&amp;rsquo;t. Thank you for displaying tremendous amounts of patience. Thank you for doing what you do. There are a few teachers in particular that have really meant a great deal to me and have really gone above and beyond in some particular way. These are(in chronological order):
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What I want to be doing in X years</title><link>/posts/x/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/x/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ahhh the age old question. The deviations of this, 	&lt;strong>&lt;strong>Where do you see yourself in x years&lt;/strong>&lt;/strong> also attempts to pry an answer akin to what this question does. It has always been weird to me. So for once and for all, I decided to write about my answer to this.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At this given time, the heuristics that I use to decide what I want to work on revolves around three main factors: curiosity/enjoyment, people I am working with, and positive impact on the world. After experimentation with work here and there, I have found that when all the above three factors are quite readily met, I’m at my happiest and produce my best work. However, if any one of the factors is problematic, that is when I grow restless or become less engaged in the world. Now, all three of the things above are very big themes/topics and leave much for interpretation. To break them down a little more to get more granularity regarding my belief:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Focus</title><link>/posts/focus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/focus/</guid><description>&lt;p>As my projects demand me to become more technical and go into heads down build mode, I find that there is a paradigm shift that happens within me to help me focus and be productive. I enter into a &amp;ldquo;meditative like&amp;rdquo; state where I block everything out and just focus on the dev work/task ahead. Here are a few things that I do in particular to help me out with this:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>/posts/posts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/posts/</guid><description>&lt;p>Heya! This is my little corner of the internet :) I hope you take a gander around and explore!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Random Things I've done</title><link>/posts/random/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/random/</guid><description>&lt;p>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of random side-quests I&amp;rsquo;ve embarked on in no particular order:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Went from 670 to 1472 in 3 months in Blitz Chess in three days bc I got bored (used to play chess before but then stopped playing for a while)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ran a marathon after running for like a year&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Slept at various airport multiple times to save money as a student. I have the art of sleeping in these situations down to a science.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Not as a student but sleeping pods in CDMX has been my most enjoyable airport snooze experience. Ask me for more stories if you see my irl&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Not eaten food for 36 hours.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Memorized 500 digits of pi in a week to win a bet/contest in high school. (I have since forgotten the last 400 but I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to erase the first 100)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Broke my phone and got completely lost in Paris while solo-travelling (second day on the continent). I did not speak the language and broke it around 6 pm. I had also dropped my stuff in my hostel (whose name/location etc. I did not remember before leaving for the day)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Became top 15 in the world in mental arithmetics in World Maths Day (&lt;a href="https://www.3plearning.com/world-maths-day/">https://www.3plearning.com/world-maths-day/&lt;/a>) when I was 12&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Learnt Abacus&lt;/li>
&lt;li>At some point in my life played the harmonium, piano, tabla (probably what I am most proficient in at this point), drums&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Crammed an entire course (and passed in uni) in 1.5 days. (I dont recommend this for things you actually want to learn but this was a required course for my program I had zero interest in)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Ate an entire pizza by myself in one sitting on a dare.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tried a four million scoville hot sauce in a hot sauce shop in Westfield Mall in SF (RIP)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Played provincially in badminton (got bronze in singles provincially twice in Grade 10 and 12), and cricket in Alberta&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>