<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Adi Sharma</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Adi Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On being the dumbest person in the room</title>
      <link>/posts/dumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/dumb/</guid>
      <description>Every now so often, I feel like I am in a room where I feel like the people I am interacting with are on a much higher level than me. The natural and the wrong reaction that I tend to exhibit is feign intelligence. This is dumb and helps nobody in the long term. The reason behind why I feign probably has ties with my System 1 (see Thinking Fast and Slow by Kahneman) kicking in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BucketList</title>
      <link>/posts/bucketlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bucketlist/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a living document Inspired by Chip Huyen&amp;rsquo;s list, I wanted to create a list of things that I&amp;rsquo;d love to someday do before I die. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I can fit all of this in one life - but I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best! Some of these are whimsical, some are more pragmatic. At any one point, you can find me trying to chase one of these -&amp;gt; currently focussed on 1 and 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Teachers</title>
      <link>/posts/tyty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tyty/</guid>
      <description>As I spend my time pent up at home during quarantine, I came to learn that one of my chemistry teachers back in high school moved down the street from our place! That was very cool and sent me down a memory lane and a flashback of high school. This teacher in particular was somebody that I always had a great time learning from. In addition to teaching Chemistry in an awesome way, she was always open to talk about life in general and as teenagers learning to take baby-steps into adulthood, these riffing sessions were so interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I want to be doing in X years</title>
      <link>/posts/x/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/x/</guid>
      <description>Ahhh the age old question. The deviations of this, Where do you see yourself in x years also attempts to pry an answer akin to what this question does. It has always been weird to me. So for once and for all, I decided to write about my answer to this.
At this given time, the heuristics that I use to decide what I want to work on revolves around three main factors: curiosity/enjoyment, people I am working with, and positive impact on the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interact Application</title>
      <link>/posts/interact-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/interact-application/</guid>
      <description>So recently, I applied to a program that I had heard great things about called Interact. The application itself was actually super fun to doand I found the questions to be very incisive and thought-provoking. This was one of the very few applications (maybe 2-3) in my entire life that I actually enjoyed finishing and even if I get in or not, I&amp;rsquo;m grateful I applied! I decided to make the answer to some of the questions public as I think they do a decent job of expressing who I am and things I care about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focus</title>
      <link>/posts/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/focus/</guid>
      <description>As my projects demand me to become more technical and go into heads down build mode, I find that there is a paradigm shift that happens within me to help me focus and be productive. I enter into a &amp;ldquo;meditative like&amp;rdquo; state where I block everything out and just focus on the dev work/task ahead. Here are a few things that I do in particular to help me out with this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/winter2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/winter2020/</guid>
      <description>Why I took Winter 2020 off? For the past three years, as a University of Waterloo student, I have gotten the opportunity to partake in four different co-ops/internships alternating between school terms. I have found these experiences to be so invaluable to my learnings as an engineering student and just as a human and I am so grateful for each one of them. However, because of this busy schedule of going back and forth between school and co-op, I found that I had very little time to explore some of the projects/passions/interests I wanted to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/posts/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/posts/</guid>
      <description>Heya! This is my little corner of the internet :) I hope you take a gander around and explore!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
