<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adi Sharma</title>
    <link>https://adityas129.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adi Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adityas129.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/posts/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/posts/posts/</guid>
      <description>Heya! This is my little corner of the internet :) I hope you take a gander around and explore!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/empty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/empty/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there - I am Adi! I am currently a Computer Engineering student at the Universiy of Waterloo with a special affinity to Deep Learning, Data Science and Engineering. Three years ago, I chose to study Engineering to learn the skills I need to make products that impact lives of many people. A lot has changed since then; my reason for doing what I do though, has not. I aspire to leverage the skills that I have to develop projects that are exciting, ambitious, vertical, and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to reach out? Feel free to contact me at adityas129@gmail.com or message me on Twitter. I&amp;rsquo;m always down for a conversation :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Events : Me</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/now/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up my life right now?
Work  T&amp;rsquo;has been a very relaxing holidays break thus far. I was able to build upon some really good habits and get into some good routines. Hoping to take that and continue that in 2020 to start the decade right! 201x has been fantastic but I am soo ready for 202x!!!! Taking this coop off(Winter 2020) to learn how to make products and ship them and bring them to life  Life Experiences  Played a bunch of board games with fam and kicked their butt while doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/habits/</guid>
      <description>As many wise men and women have said, compounding results are very real and this advice could not be more relevant to anything more than habits. I hope to use this as a space to track all habits that I have successfully integrated into my lifestyle. In this case, success is defined as persisting the habit for &amp;gt; 21 days consecutively.
 Making my bed right upon waking up Doing pushups upon first step out of bed 5 minute Journal 1 LC question a day  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditations</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/meditations/</guid>
      <description>This is a space where I just note down random shit that comes to me:
 Freedom in this day and age is directly proportional to courage Essentialism is the key to progress Discipline is freedom - Jocko Willink (I think that&amp;rsquo;s how it&amp;rsquo;s spelled?) Hooks/Systems are the best way to cultivate productive behaviour AI safety is insanely important Knowledge needs to become decentralized I don&amp;rsquo;t need to wait to get to an X position to do meaningful work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Brain Hardware: Step away, Neuralink. Currently in incubation :)
 Nearer: Nearby Object Detector for Bicycles using Ultrasonic sensors
 LabelLearn: This project aims to enable a labeller to be consistent with both their fellow labelers and their past self while seeing the live class distribution of the dataset.
 Sundae: A text based journaling chatbot that uses NLP and sentimental analysis to cheer you up!
 Messiah: Messiah is an oracle management interface that developers can interact with to get the most reliable data from blockchains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/questions/</guid>
      <description>Is a calm mind better or one with a bunch of crazy ideas? How do I manage information intake? What aspects of my identity are worth preserving? How do I conquer the mind and it&amp;rsquo;s primal needs? How do I rapidly iterate my understanding of a very niche area and become a domain expert? How should I increase my rate of learning as a developer? Is specialization in technical skills worth it or is being a generalist more aligned for my goals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readings</title>
      <link>https://adityas129.github.io/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adityas129.github.io/reading/</guid>
      <description>books List of all books that I have read and their reviews
 Skin in the Game by Taleb Meditations by Aurelius Bhagvat Gita Shoe Dog Coming Storm Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game Deep Work So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You Zero to One Ego is the Enemy  List of Books I want to re-read
 Zero to One Deep Work So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You Meditations by Aurelius Bhagvat Gita  Book Wish list</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>