<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adi Sharma</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adi Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/posts/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/posts/posts/</guid>
      <description>Heya! This is my little corner of the internet :) I hope you take a gander around and explore!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there - I am Adi! I am currently a Computer Engineering student at the Universiy of Waterloo with a special affinity to Deep Learning, Data Science and Engineering. Three years ago, I chose to study Engineering to learn the skills I need to make products that impact lives of many people. A lot has changed since then; my reason for doing what I do though, has not. I aspire to leverage the skills that I have to develop projects that are exciting, ambitious, vertical, and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to reach out? Feel free to contact me at adityas129@gmail.com or message me on Twitter. I&amp;rsquo;m always down for a conversation :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Events : Me</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/now/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up my life right now?
Work  August 12th, &amp;lsquo;19 : Battled with personal portfolio  Life Experiences  August 10th, &amp;lsquo;19 : Went out with Matt and Tony to Taste of Danforth!! Ate a few spinach pies, smashed some plates and yelled OPA and had a whole bunch of fun! We then went to Trinity Bellwoods to play Ulti + Soccer - in an attempt to bicycle kick, almost had a concussion lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/habits/</guid>
      <description>As many wise men and women have said, compounding results are very real and this advice could not be more relevant to anything more than habits. I hope to use this as a space to track all habits that I have successfully integrated into my lifestyle. In this case, success is defined as persisting the habit for &amp;gt; 21 days consecutively.
 Making my bed right upon waking up Doing pushups upon first step out of bed  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditations</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/meditations/</guid>
      <description>This is a space where I just note down random shit that comes to me:
 Freedom in this day and age is directly proportional to courage Essentialism is the key to progress Discipline is freedom - Jocko Willink (I think that&amp;rsquo;s how it&amp;rsquo;s spelled?) Hooks/Systems are the best way to cultivate productive behaviour AI safety is insanely important Knowledge needs to become decentralized  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/</guid>
      <description> Brain Hardware: Step away, Neuralink. Currently in incubation :)
 Sundae: A text based journaling chatbot that uses NLP and sentimental analysis to cheer you up!
 MyoVision: A workout assister that uses Myo and statistics to improve your posture while also serving as a tracker of your activity.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/questions/</guid>
      <description> Is a calm mind better or one with a bunch of crazy ideas? How do I manage information intake? What aspects of my identity are worth preserving? How do I conquer the mind and it&amp;rsquo;s primal needs? How do I rapidly iterate my understanding of a very niche area and become a domain expert?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readings</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/reading/</guid>
      <description>books List of all books that I have read and their reviews
 Skin in the Game by Taleb Meditations by Aurelius Bhagvat Gita Shoe Dog Coming Storm Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game Deep Work So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You  List of Books I want to re-read
 Deep Work So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You Meditations by Aurelius Bhagvat Gita  Book Wish list
 Black Swan by Taleb</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>