<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adi Sharma</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adi Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interact Application</title>
      <link>/posts/interact-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/interact-application/</guid>
      <description>So recently, I applied to a program that I had heard great things about called Interact. The application itself was actually super fun to doand I found the questions to be very incisive and thought-provoking. This was one of the very few applications (maybe 2-3) in my entire life that I actually enjoyed finishing and even if I get in or not, I&amp;rsquo;m grateful I applied! I decided to make the answer to some of the questions public as I think they do a decent job of expressing who I am and things I care about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Focus</title>
      <link>/posts/focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/focus/</guid>
      <description>Focus As my projects demand me to become more technical and go into heads down build mode, I find that there is a paradigm shift that happens within me to help me focus and be productive. I enter into a &amp;ldquo;meditative like&amp;rdquo; state where I block everything out and just focus on the dev work/task ahead. Here are a few things that I do in particular to help me out with this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/winter2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/winter2020/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Why I took Winter 2020 off? -- Why I took Winter 2020 off? For the past three years, as a University of Waterloo student, I have gotten the opportunity to partake in four different co-ops/internships alternating between school terms. I have found these experiences to be so invaluable to my learnings as an engineering student and just as a human and I am so grateful for each one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/posts/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/posts/</guid>
      <description>Heya! This is my little corner of the internet :) I hope you take a gander around and explore!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there - I am Adi! I am currently a Computer Engineering student at the Universiy of Waterloo with a special affinity to Deep Learning, Data Science and Engineering. Three years ago, I chose to study Engineering to learn the skills I need to make products that impact lives of many people. A lot has changed since then; my reason for doing what I do though, has not. I aspire to leverage the skills that I have to develop projects that are exciting, ambitious, vertical, and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to reach out? Feel free to contact me at adityas129@gmail.com or message me on Twitter. I&amp;rsquo;m always down for a conversation :)

PS: Also, thanks for stopping by, here&amp;rsquo;s a cookie for you </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Events : Me</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up my life right now?
Last Updated: Jan 28th 2020
Work  Currently working on two projects: building a tool to reinvent the way we present and a tool to boost productivity (I know what you are thinking, not another one of these - i swear this is different) Have not progressed much on the ML learning side of the things - hope to fix that soon  Life Experiences  real talk : GP seems kinda boring now that most of the people my age are not in town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a living document &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Over the years, while exploring on the internet, I come across pages/sites that really captivate me and capture my curiosity. I wish to keep a list of all these places for future reference and for the world to see and explore:
 Celine: How to Build a Biotech &amp;nbsp;
 Tristan Hume: Cool Waterloo developer! &amp;nbsp;
 Dan Wang: Lots of deep dives into interesting topics &amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditations</title>
      <link>/meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditations/</guid>
      <description>This is a space where I just note down random ideas and thoughts that come to me:
 Habits are really powerful tools that when utilized properly, have exponential returns. When it comes to this topic, something that I try to keep at the back of my mind is just how much could be accomplished in a year if everyday, I choose to be 1% better than I was yesterday. Freedom in this day and age is directly proportional to courage Essentialism is the key to progress Discipline is freedom - Jocko Willink (I think that&amp;rsquo;s how it&amp;rsquo;s spelled?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
 Brain Hardware: In progress - learning more about BCI as I go at it :) &amp;nbsp;
 Nearer: Nearby Object Detector for Bicycles using Ultrasonic sensors &amp;nbsp;
 LabelLearn: This project aims to enable a labeller to be consistent with both their fellow labelers and their past self while seeing the live class distribution of the dataset. &amp;nbsp;
 Sundae: A text based journaling chatbot that uses NLP and sentimental analysis to cheer you up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/</guid>
      <description>Questions that I struggle with to this day
 Is a calm mind better or one with a bunch of crazy ideas? How do I manage information intake? What aspects of my identity are worth preserving? How do I conquer the mind and it&amp;rsquo;s primal needs? How do I rapidly iterate my understanding of a very niche area and become a domain expert? How should I increase my rate of learning as a developer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readings</title>
      <link>/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of Books I&amp;rsquo;m currently reading  Dune Courage to be Disliked
 Lean Startup &amp;nbsp;  List of all books that I have read and would recommend  Skin in the Game by Taleb Meditations by Aurelius Bhagvat Gita Shoe Dog Coming Storm Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game Deep Work So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You Zero to One Ego is the Enemy &amp;nbsp;  Interesting book lists that I sometimes refer to  Patrick Collison</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>