<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adi Sharma</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adi Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/winter2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/winter2020/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Why I took Winter 2020 off? -- Why I took Winter 2020 off? For the past three years, as a University of Waterloo student, I have gotten the opportunity to partake in four different co-ops/internships alternating between school terms. I have found these experiences to be so invaluable to my learnings as an engineering student and just as a human and I am so grateful for each one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/posts/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/posts/</guid>
      <description>Heya! This is my little corner of the internet :) I hope you take a gander around and explore!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there - I am Adi! I am currently a Computer Engineering student at the Universiy of Waterloo with a special affinity to Deep Learning, Data Science and Engineering. Three years ago, I chose to study Engineering to learn the skills I need to make products that impact lives of many people. A lot has changed since then; my reason for doing what I do though, has not. I aspire to leverage the skills that I have to develop projects that are exciting, ambitious, vertical, and impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Want to reach out? Feel free to contact me at adityas129@gmail.com or message me on Twitter. I&amp;rsquo;m always down for a conversation :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Events : Me</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up my life right now?
Work  T&amp;rsquo;has been a very relaxing holidays break thus far. I was able to build upon some really good habits and get into some good routines. Hoping to take that and continue that in 2020 to start the decade right! 201x has been fantastic but I am soo ready for 202x!!!! Taking this coop off(Winter 2020) to learn how to make products and ship them and bring them to life  Life Experiences  Played a bunch of board games with fam and kicked their butt while doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habits</title>
      <link>/habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/habits/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Habits are really powerful tools that when utilized properly, have exponential returns. When it comes to this topic, something that I try to keep at the back of my mind is just how much could be accomplished in a year if everyday, I choose to be 1% better than I was yesterday. This, of course, applies to the contrary as well:
​ 0.99365 = 0.03 
​ 1365 = 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/links/</guid>
      <description>Over the years, while exploring on the internet, I come across pages/sites that really captivate me and capture my curiosity. I wish to keep a list of all these places for future reference and for the world to see and explore:
 How to Build a Biotech &amp;nbsp;
 Cool Waterloo dev person &amp;nbsp;
 Lots of deep dives into interesting topics &amp;nbsp;
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditations</title>
      <link>/meditations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditations/</guid>
      <description>This is a space where I just note down random ideas and thoughts that come to me:
 Freedom in this day and age is directly proportional to courage Essentialism is the key to progress Discipline is freedom - Jocko Willink (I think that&amp;rsquo;s how it&amp;rsquo;s spelled?) Hooks/Systems are the best way to cultivate productive behaviour AI safety is insanely important Knowledge needs to become decentralized I don&amp;rsquo;t need to wait to get to an X position to do meaningful work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
 Brain Hardware: In progress - learning more about BCI as I go at it :) &amp;nbsp;
 Nearer: Nearby Object Detector for Bicycles using Ultrasonic sensors &amp;nbsp;
 LabelLearn: This project aims to enable a labeller to be consistent with both their fellow labelers and their past self while seeing the live class distribution of the dataset. &amp;nbsp;
 Sundae: A text based journaling chatbot that uses NLP and sentimental analysis to cheer you up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions</title>
      <link>/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/questions/</guid>
      <description>Questions that I struggle with to this day
 Is a calm mind better or one with a bunch of crazy ideas? How do I manage information intake? What aspects of my identity are worth preserving? How do I conquer the mind and it&amp;rsquo;s primal needs? How do I rapidly iterate my understanding of a very niche area and become a domain expert? How should I increase my rate of learning as a developer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readings</title>
      <link>/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/</guid>
      <description>List of Books I&amp;rsquo;m currently reading  Tribes of Mentors Can&amp;rsquo;t Hurt Me Atomic Habits &amp;nbsp;  List of all books that I have read and would recommend  Skin in the Game by Taleb Meditations by Aurelius Bhagvat Gita Shoe Dog Coming Storm Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game Deep Work So Good They Can&amp;rsquo;t Ignore You Zero to One Ego is the Enemy &amp;nbsp;  Interesting book lists  Black Swan by Taleb</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>